<application>
  <component name="AppStorage">
    <histories>
      <item value="doctype" />
      <item value="activity live room pad room top container" />
      <item value="stable" />
      <item value="This version of the Android Support plugin for IntelliJ IDEA (or Android Studio) cannot open this project, please retry with version 4.3 or newer." />
      <item value="External System Exception" />
      <item value=") cannot open this project, please retry with version 4.3 or newer" />
      <item value="cannot open this project, please retry with version 4.3 or newer" />
      <item value="private Lookup In" />
      <item value="java.lang.invoke.MethodHandles.privateLookupIn(java.lang.Class, java.lang.invoke.MethodHandles$Lookup)" />
      <item value="Yearly Goals" />
      <item value="Recipes" />
      <item value="Score /5" />
      <item value="Publishing/Release Date" />
      <item value="Property" />
      <item value="Summary" />
      <item value="Publisher" />
      <item value="The modern day reading list includes more than just books. We've created a dashboard to help you track books, articles, podcasts, and videos. Each media type has its own view based on the Type property.   Change your views to sort content by status, author, type, or publisher ✓ Rate content out of 5 stars ✓" />
      <item value="基础" />
      <item value="虚拟" />
      <item value="FAQ How is the free Personal Plan different from the Personal Pro and Team Plans? The biggest difference is how you can collaborate with others.  The free Personal Plan is designed for individual use, but allows up to 5 unique guests. These are friends, family members, and others you can invite to collaborate with you privately on any page. You can also share a page publicly and turn on commenting or editing access. In the Share menu at the top right, turn on &quot;Share to web&quot; then &quot;Allow editing.&quot; Any Notion user with the link will be able to edit your page.  With the Personal Pro Plan, you can invite unlimited guests for private collaboration. For example, if you run your own business, you can invite all your clients to provide feedback on your work.  With the Team Plan, you can add members to your workspace so you all share and work on the same content. It also comes with more permission and admin controls so you and your teammates can work together securely. See the plan comparison chart for more details.  What happens when I go over the guest limit on my Personal Plan? Upgrade to the Personal Pro Plan for unlimited guests, or the Team Plan if you collaborate with the same group of people automatically. You can also review and remove inactive guests in Settings &amp; Members.  How do I try out the Team Plan for free? When asked how you would like to set up Notion during sign up, select Team, and you’ll be automatically enrolled in a Team Plan trial. You’ll get access to most features of a paid Team Plan, with a 1,000 block storage limit. If your team wants to add more than that, upgrade to the full Team Plan. Details above.  What happens when I go over the block storage limit on my Team trial? You can still read, edit, and organize existing content blocks as usual, but you won’t be able to add new content blocks.  However, you can delete existing content blocks to free up your storage.  Can I use Notion for free? Absolutely! Notion is free to use indefinitely.  The Personal Plan is completely free for individual use. The Team Plan has a free trial with a 1,000 block limit, more than enough to try out Notion with your team before upgrading.  What is a block? A block is any single piece of content you add to your page, like a paragraph of text, a to-do item, an image, a code block, an embedded file, etc. Think of your page as being made up of these building blocks.  Can I delete blocks to free up my storage? Of course! It works just like the storage limit on your phone or computer. If you delete something, you will free up space for more.  Do you offer student discounts? The Personal Pro Plan is free for students and educators. This lets you collaborate with unlimited guests and gives you version history. Simply sign up with your school email address and you’ll immediately gain access to these features.  If you’re already on a Personal Pro Plan, change the email associated with your account to your school email address to get it for free. If you're already on our free Education Plan, you've been automatically upgraded to the Personal Pro Plan.   How do I earn credit? You can earn credit by using Notion across your devices and trying out new features. Go to the Earn Credit tab in Settings &amp; Members to learn more.  How do I apply credit to my workspace? To apply credit, you must first upgrade to a paid plan. As part of this process, you can choose to apply some or all of your account credit to the plan.  Why do you need my billing information if I have enough credit to pay for Notion? We still require your billing information, even if you applied enough credit to make your first bill $0, because you may run out of credit in the future and we need to be able to charge your account.  What happens if I run out of credit? If you run out of credit, your account will be charged via your selected payment method.  Is there a maximum amount of credit I can earn? Yes, you can earn up to $200 in credit.  What advanced permissions does the paid Team &amp; Enterprise Plans offer? If you are on a free Team trial, you can set the access level on each page to &quot;Full access,&quot; &quot;Can view,&quot; or &quot;Can comment.&quot; That dictates how other users can interact with that page. &quot;Full access&quot; means someone can edit, comment, and share the page with others.  On paid Team and Enterprise Plans, you have the ability to grant &quot;Can edit&quot; access to other users. This gives someone the ability to edit and comment on that page, but not share it with others. This is especially useful if you do not want your content leaking outside your team.   What admin tools come with the Team Plan? On a free Team trial, every member in your workspace is an admin. This means all of you can adjust team settings and invite other people into the workspace.  If you want only a few people to have admin abilities, we recommend upgrading to the full Team Plan. It comes with tools that allow you to make only select people admins while everyone else is a member. Members can't edit billing information or security options, and can't share your content outside the workspace.  How is pricing calculated for the Personal Pro Plan? If you upgrade your workspace to Personal Pro, you will be charged a flat fee ($5 monthly or $48 yearly).  Guests are free of charge, but they can only be added to one page at a time.  How is pricing calculated for the Team Plan? If you upgrade your workspace to the Team Plan, you will be charged a fee per member ($10 monthly or $96 yearly). For example, if you pay per month and have 5 members, you will be charged $50 each month.  Guests are free of charge – but they can only access individual pages they are invited to. In other words, guests won’t be able to see all the team pages under the &quot;Workspace&quot; section in the left sidebar.  Do you have monthly and yearly billing options? Yes! We offer both monthly and yearly billing options. The yearly billing option is always cheaper (an estimated 20% discount). For example, the Team Plan is $10 per member per month when you choose the monthly option, but $8 per member per month if you choose to pay yearly.  How does adding and removing members work? Whether you're on a monthly or yearly billing schedule, your account may be charged on a monthly basis if you make these types of changes. If you added members, your account will be charged a prorated amount based on the percentage of the billing cycle left at the time each member was added. If you removed members, your account will be credited in the same way.  What happens when I change plans? Upgrading or downgrading your plan works similarly to adding and removing members. Your account will be charged or credited based on the percentage of the billing cycle left at the time the plan was changed.  What happens if I cancel my paid plan? When you cancel your plan, you will remain on the plan until the end of your billing cycle, at which time the plan will be canceled.  What happens if my payment fails? Like if my credit card expires? Your account email will be notified after each failed payment. Payments may be retried up to 4 times within the next month. After this, if the payment did not succeed, you will be downgraded to the free plan.  Can I change my payment method? You can change your payment method at any time in your billing settings.  Do you offer refunds? In most cases, we don't offer refunds. Instead, we'll credit your account a prorated amount if you remove members from your workspace or downgrade. The next time your account is charged, any remaining balance will be used before creating a new charge.  Do you have a Service-Level Agreement (SLA)? We do not offer a standard SLA. For teams with greater than 100 members, we can offer a custom SLA.   How does importing content from another app affect my block storage limit if I'm on the Team Plan trial? Content created via import doesn’t count toward your workspace’s storage limit. We want to make sure you get started with Notion as smoothly as possible.  How is my payment being processed? We use Stripe to process your payment. It’s the same payment provider used by products such as Twitter, Pinterest, and Lyft. We do not handle your credit card information directly.  Can I belong to multiple teams on Notion? Yes! You can use the same email address to create and join multiple teams. However, each one of these workspaces is on its own plan and needs to be upgraded individually." />
      <item value="Guests" />
      <item value="Pay annually Monthly" />
      <item value="Admin tools" />
      <item value="Version history" />
      <item value="Unlimited" />
      <item value="This workspace is on the Personal Plan. Upgrade to collaborate with more people using Notion." />
      <item value="Credit balance" />
      <item value="Your current credit balance is $5. That's equivalent to 1 month of the Personal Pro Plan." />
      <item value="Your current email is zhao1027313530@gmail.com. We've sent a temporary verification code to this email." />
      <item value="Use this template to track your personal tasks. Click + New to create a new task directly on this board. Click an existing task to add additional context or subtasks." />
      <item value="Weekly Agenda" />
      <item value="Job Applications" />
      <item value="Resume" />
      <item value="Life Wiki" />
      <item value="Habit Tracker" />
      <item value="Simple Notebook" />
      <item value="Blog Post" />
      <item value="Travel Planner" />
      <item value="Goals" />
      <item value="personal" />
      <item value="Course Schedule" />
      <item value="Lesson Plans" />
      <item value="Classroom Home" />
      <item value="Syllabus" />
      <item value="Simple Budget" />
      <item value="Roommate Home" />
      <item value="Personal CRM 、" />
      <item value="Cornell Notes System" />
      <item value="Thesis Planning " />
      <item value="Quick Note" />
    </histories>
    <option name="languageScores">
      <map>
        <entry key="CHINESE" value="1876" />
        <entry key="ENGLISH" value="1877" />
        <entry key="ARABIC" value="1" />
        <entry key="BULGARIAN" value="1" />
        <entry key="DANISH" value="1" />
        <entry key="FRENCH" value="7" />
        <entry key="FINNISH" value="1" />
        <entry key="DUTCH" value="2" />
        <entry key="LATIN" value="3" />
        <entry key="ROMANIAN" value="4" />
        <entry key="MALAGASY" value="1" />
        <entry key="MALAY" value="2" />
        <entry key="NORWEGIAN" value="1" />
        <entry key="PORTUGUESE" value="1" />
        <entry key="SWEDISH" value="1" />
        <entry key="SLOVAK" value="1" />
        <entry key="GREEK" value="1" />
        <entry key="ITALIAN" value="1" />
        <entry key="INDONESIAN" value="3" />
        <entry key="VIETNAMESE" value="1" />
      </map>
    </option>
  </component>
  <component name="Settings">
    <option name="ignoreRegExp" value="" />
  </component>
</application>